bag-all.com 2019-05-14

# Privacy Policy - Bag-all

_This is Bag-all:s privacy policy, updated May 24th 2018.  At Bag-all, we keep your information in the strictest confidence. We never give, sell, or trade your information. If you wish to be added to our mailing list, you will receive emails updating you about new store products, sales and events._

We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.   

Yes! Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow it) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.   

The content of our web site (including text, graphics, logos, images) is the property of Bag-all and is protected by United States and international copyright laws. You may electronically copy and print hard copies of pages from this web site as long as you mention Bag-all as the source of the content.  

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below: email: info@bag-all.com

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: – To personalize your experience - your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs. – To improve our website - we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you. – To improve customer service - your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs. – To process transactions - your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. – To send periodic emails -The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.   

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

Bag-all.com may contain links to web sites operated by other third parties. Bag-all does not endorse or assume any responsibility for these web sites. We have no control over, or responsibility for, their content, information or activities.

The trademarks, logos, service marks and trade names of Bag-all and our affiliates may not be used without our written permission. ERRORS AND INACCURACIES We do not represent or warrant that the information on our web site is accurate, complete, or current. This includes pricing and availability information. We reserve the right to correct any errors or omissions, and to change or update information at any time without prior notice.  

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems and who are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.  

By visiting our web site, you agree that the laws of the State of New York will govern these Terms of Use and any dispute of any sort that might arise, without regard to principles of conflict of law.

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. YOUR CONSENT By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.  

Except for information necessary to place an order, any comments or other submissions sent to us will be deemed non-confidential, and shall be the property of Bag-all, including worldwide rights in all intellectual properties.

We make no representations or warranties, express or implied, with respect to this web site. Its content, and the information and services available on or through it, are provided "as is." Except as otherwise provided under applicable laws, we and our affiliates will not be liable for any damages whatsoever arising out of or related to the use of this web site.
